Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 11.02.24 14:08:13
Announcer: Calamari  stolen the lead, but Ample Parking is making strides,
and is now at fourth, third, and holding second place, while Blue Calamari is at steady speed.
And down the stretch they come! Ample Parking comes from behind.
It's Ample Parking by a nose!
This is the last call for the third race.
You may still wager if you hurry. Here's your information on the race ...
让开，瘸子来了
Out of the way. Cripple coming through.
6号买金子输
Um, 6 race at Golden Downs. I'll take the two and the four.
2块买4号
嘿，那是我的生日
Hey, that's my birthday. February 4th, 1963. I think that's a good bet?
2月4号
我看这会是个不错的赌注
Oh, wh-what's your birthday?
你的生日是多少？
Take your time. Don't worry. There's only 30 seconds to post.
慢慢来
Is there any way I can bet on the 6 and the 3 also?
别担心只有30秒钟下注的时间
You know, for the year? All four horses. Can I do that?
有没有办法我再买3号第2位 一整年，我可以那么做么？
He wants a $2.00 exacta box - 2, 4, 6, 3. Give him $24.
他要买2号整注，给他24块
该你了
Mm-hmm.
3号马买赢，终结者赢
Your turn.
整个一注，复合赛胜出
9th at Gulfstream Park. 500 on the three horse. Seminal Uprising to win.
干脆烧钱算了
我要燃烧我的胜利
Might as well burn your money.
火焰更烈
I'll burn my winnings. Bigger flame.
Announcer: Ladies and gentlemen...
买同样的注
Same race, TermiGator to win.
Flag is up.
终结者赢
- Sorry, race just closed. - Damn it.
对不起，到时间了
真该死
She was 14 to 1, too.
是1/14的赔率
That fat ass over there just saved you money.
那就用那个胖屁股去省钱吧
- No way Seminal Uprising is... - I don't bet on the horses.
你不必那么辛辣吧
I bet on the jocks. My rider is bulimic.
我意思是马屁股
我的坐骑会赢
Purses after his weigh-ins.
在最终的第8局
Leave a 2-pound pile at the starting gate, shaves valuable time of that final 8th.
它一定会胜出的
有小道消息真棒
Nice to have inside information.
Leads at the stretch by a length, the Burning Bush. And on the level is Andy right up on the inside...
[Clash and thud]
[Breathes with difficulty]
这有医生吗?
Is anybody here a doctor?
[Breathes with difficulty]
找感觉呢?
You tryin' to cop a feel?
我在青年会学过急救课程
I took a CPR class at the Y.
如果她不是抽筋而是犯 心脏病那没准有用
That would be useful if she was having a heart atack instead of seizure.
抽筋？要把她的舌头压下去么？
Seizure? Hold her tangue down?
如果你想把手指咬掉的话
If you wanna get a finger bitten off. Call an ambulance.
叫急救车
Methodistis 3 blocks down. I could drive her.
急救站就在3条街外
－我可以开车送她 －打电话吧
Just make the call.
那是什么鬼东西?
Man: What the hell is that?
我怎么会知道?
How should I know?
告诉急救人员把她送到PP医院去
Tell the paramedics to take her to Princeton-Plainsborough.
医生名叫豪斯
The doctor's name is House.
终结者以两个身长获胜
And it's TermiGator winning by 2 lengths!
2x09 - Deception
House - [豪斯医生] 第二季 第九集
Original Airdate (FOX): 13-DEC-2005
我真纳闷豪斯怎么会 对那些电视屏那么上瘾
This is one does House hang out at OTB?
那家伙是个瘾君子
Man's an addict.
是，是对药品成瘾，不是赌博
Right, addicted to pills, not gambling.
那是同类事件：药品成瘾，酗酒，赌博
Same thing - drug abuse, drinking, gambling.
它们都可以激活脑部欣快中枢
They all fire up the same pleasure centers in the brain.
成瘾就是成瘾……
An addict is an addict is...
赌博又不能把他的痛感带走
Gambling doesn't take away his pain.
我赢了的话就可以
It does when I win.
火辣的赌马宝贝
Hot OTB babe has grand mal and inexplicable bruising.
癫痫发作
身上有不明原因的瘀伤
-那又怎样? -她开始抽搐的时候你就在边上 那么站着么？
What up with that?
You were just standing there and she started to seize?
花点跟我一样多的时间跟真人在一起
Spend as much time around the real people as I do, someone gets sick.
会有人生病的
Platelets are 89. She's anemic.
血小板89
她贫血
而且她血液酒精浓度是1.3
And she has a blood alcohol level of .13.
火辣的赌马宝贝?
Hot OTB babe?
显然是个妓女
Obviously a working girl. Probably an STD, infection.
没准是站街的，感染
不发热，没感染
No fever, no infection.
酒精滥用可以解释
Alcohol abuse explains it all.
导致抽搐并影响她血液的凝结能力
Causes seizures and affects her blood's ability to clot, which causes bruising.
从而导致瘀伤
Start her on heparin. She'll be fine by morning.
给她一点肝磷脂，早晨就没事了
但是她的瘀伤并没有斑点
Except for the fact that the bruises are not petechial, which means it's not DIC.
所以不是dic
那瘀伤就是由外伤造成的
So the bruises were caused by trauma.
她也许被她男朋友痛打 或是批条客
She probably got beat up by her boyfriend. Or her pimp.
未见其人先行评价叫什么来着？
What's that called when you judge someone before ever meeting them?
她是场外赌博的常客
She's a regular at OTB.
反正不觉得她是朝九晚五族 家庭主妇族
Somehow I don't see her holding down a 9-to-5 and going to PTA meetings.
我在场
I was there.
我有个朝九晚三的工作
I have a "9-to-3" job.
可能是sle 家族毛细血管扩张症
It could be SLE, familial telangiectasis,
甚至是库辛症
- or even Cushing's. - Good. Start with those.
好，由这些入手吧
－哪一个？ －库辛症
- Which one? - Cushing's.
可以解释抽搐和瘀伤
Explains the seizure and the bruising.
但不能解释贫血
Not the anemia.
她没吃很多肉
So she doesn't eat a lot of meat.
酗酒导致Dic更贴切
DIC brought on by alcohol abuse is far more likely. Do a full workup.
做全套检查吧
H and P. And lab her up, LP, MRI.
H和P，给她建实验室档案
lp和mri.
Wh-Whoa!
哇……
你刚才是明确下令 让我去找她的医疗记录么?
Did you just ever-so-subtly order me to get her medical history?
卡迪上周起让我负责了，所以……
Cuddy put me in charge last week. So...yeah.
对的
是假装负责
It was a pretend in charge.
在诉讼结束前遮掩一下
Formality to get past the suits in legal.
对，那些许可证批准人员喜欢化装 舞会和假装的玩意
Right, those licensing board folk love to play dress-up and pretend.
嘿，别担心
Hey, no worries. I'll let you keep your parking space.
我会让你留着你的停车位
你可以用
You can have it.
你还需要我的残疾人授勋仪式
You'll also need my handicapped placard.
俯身过来
Bend over.
好了，你的论点够明确的了
Well, you make a pretty convincing argument.
小蔡杀了那女人 现在福满又负责了？
Chase killed that woman. Now Foreman's in charge?
对，我们是论资排辈的
Yeah, we have a pecking order here.
如果卡麦伦杀了什么人 就又轮到小蔡了
If Cameron kills somebody, Chase takes over. There's a flow chart in the lobby.
大厅里有流程表
在接下了的3周里 你直接向福满医生报告
For the next three weeks, you answer directly to Dr. Foreman.
而我希望你能9点来参加查房
And I expect you here for grand rounds at 9:00.
顺便提...
By the way... I like sugar in my coffee.
我的咖啡里喜欢加糖
如果不灵光，那是你的不灵光
If there's a screw-up, it's your screw-up.
你别指望豪斯医生给你兜底
You won't have Dr. House to fall back on.
"你系安全带了么?"
"Do you wear a seat belt?"
- 那真的跟抽搐有关么? - 跳
Is that really relevant to a seizure?
“你接种过牛痘么？” 这问题怎么样？
Skip it.
How about, um...
"Were you vaccinated for polio?"
我觉得你是为了得到fdr才给我表格的
I think you gave me the form intended for FDR.
你真喜欢第5名的那个小莫么?
You really like Teeny Tiny Mo in the 5th?
我昨天赌中了6局中的4
I went 4 for 6 yesterday.
你想赢，先把我治好
You want winners, cure me first.
"你对你的人生大体上还满意么?"
"Are you generally satisfied with your life?"
才没问那样的问题呢
It does not ask that.
你知道，我其实正打算问一位有名望的 医生在场外赌马大厅干嘛？
You know, I was going to ask
what a respectable doctor was doing in an OTB parlor.
可不知怎么，那个问题不重要了
Somehow that question doesn't seem relevant anymore.
你的借口呢?
- What's your excuse? - Turns me on.
让我兴奋莫名
Yeah? What else turns you on?
是么？还有什么让你兴奋莫名的？
药品?
Drugs?
不经意的性生活?
Casual sex?
粗野的性生活?
Rough sex?
不经意的粗野的性生活?
Casual rough sex?
我是医生，我需要知道
I'm a doctor. I need to know.
没性生活，刚搬来的
No sex.
甚至都还没找到工作呢 谁都不认识
Just moved here.
Haven't even found a job yet. Don't know anybody.
没工作就跑这来？
Came here without a job.
那意思是你并不是搬到这来
That means you didn't move here.
你是从什么地方逃走到这的
You moved away from somewhere else.
Whew.
- 疼么? - 不
- Does that hurt? - No.
在吃出处方药么？ 荷尔蒙？强的松？
You on prescription meds? Hormones? Prednisone?
我已经回答过那个问题了
I already answered that one. I think it was question number 20-something.
我想是第20号问题什么的
对，我可以一伸手就拿到
Yeah, and I could reach down and get it,
可那不就破坏我的整体酷形象了么？
but that would kind of spoil the whole cool move.
我没吃什么药
I'm not on any medications.
你吃素么?
- You vegetarian? - No. Why?
不是，为什么问？
因为你可能得了所谓库辛综合症
Because you might have something called Cushing's Syndrome.
那意思是……
Which basically means...
我的垂体分泌过量促肾上腺皮质激素
My pituitary is overproducing ACTH,
导致我的肾上腺
which is causing my adrenal glands
向我的血流中推进过多皮质醇
to push too much cortisol into my bloodstream.
很巧合，我也是个医生
By coincidence,
我从去年患上的
I'm a doctor too.
Yeah, I had it last year.
他们动了脑科手术
They did brain surgery.
从我的垂体里移除了一个腺瘤
Removed an adenoma from my pituitary.
[Whistles a tune]
嗯?
Huh?
你刚才说什么?
What did you just say?
"你是对的，豪斯，她的腺体瘤又长了
"You were right, House, her pituitary tumor regrew.
是库辛症，你真神了"
It is Cushing's. Uncanny how you do that."
其实，那是卡麦伦的主意
Actually, it was Cameron's idea.
不，卡麦伦有过3个主意
No, Cameron had three ideas.
我选了其一进行鼓励和培养
I chose one to encourage, to nurture.
没错，你就是养分
Yeah, you're all about the nurturing.
你需要拥抱么?
Do you need a hug?
我没看到又长的痕迹
I don't see any regrowth.
你拿到她医疗记录的传真了么?
You get a medical records fax over?
聪明的工作，不是勤奋的工作 那是我的哲学，老板
Work smart, not hard. That's my philosophy, boss.
我当你说没拿
I'll take that as a no.
安尼卡，我需要你纹丝不动
Foreman: Anica, I need you to stay completely still.
对不起
Sorry.
还是什么都没看到
Still don't see anything.
好，那就是微型瘤，肉眼看不到
Okay, so it's a micro adenoma, too small to see.
微型到根本不在那的程度
It's so small, it's not even there.
对，我能预言她在一年前
Right, it's just a coincidence that I predicted a rare condition that shehappened to have a year ago.
发生稀有症状完全是出于偶然
她的LP检查结果出来了么?
Results from her LP back yet?
没做LP，我知道她怎么回事
Didn't do an LP. I knew what she had.
Window Closed [control panel: open_winMRI-1]
去做LP
Go do the LP.
好，我需要你向一侧翻身
Okay, I need you to roll over on your side, kiss your kneecaps.
吻你的膝盖
舞会时间到
Party time.
－我以为只需要一位医生做这个 －我来观察
I thought it only took one doctor to do this. I'm observing.
她到这来是要保证我不把你搞瘫痪
She's here to make sure I don't paralyze you.
以前你做过这个，对吧?
You've done this before, right?
成功的么?
Successfully?
他在开玩笑，他是个超凡的医生
He's kidding. He's an excellent doctor.
我要用利多卡因使你局部麻醉
House: I'm gonna numb the area with some lidocaine.
然后我们就结束比赛了
And then we're off to the races. See what I did there?
看我在那是怎么干的了么?
I used horse racing jargon to make the patient feel more comfortable.
我用赌马的行话使病人感觉更舒适
好，来吧
Okay, here we go.
感觉上是骨头，那样疼么?
[Gasps] Ow!
Felt like bone. Does that hurt?
一点点，你干嘛呢？ 嗷！
A little bit. What are you doing? Oww!
试试把背往后一点
Try running your back a bit more.
现在这样就挺好
Perfect is the way you are.
哦，都赖我
- [Gasps] - Oops. That was all me.
该向下挪一节椎骨
Ow!
Might wanna move down one vertebrae.
这比我记忆中难多了
This is actually much harder than I remember.
哦!
[Gasps] Ohh!
我的胸部有压迫感
My chest feels a little tight.
深呼吸
Try taking a deep breath.
豪斯医生，还是由我来接手吧
Dr. House, maybe I should take it from here.
第8次是魔法次数
Eighth time's the charm.
啊!
Aah!
你想惹福满生气么?
You trying to piss off Foreman?
让……
[Monitor stars beeping] Let...
血压是240比140
Cameron: EP's 240 over 140.
把那个东西关了，好么?
Turn that thing off, will you?
把针拔出来
Take the needle out.
- 把针拔出来 - 好吧
- Take the needle out! - Okay!
是高血压临界点
It's a hypertensive crisis. Start her on an IV Lopressor drip.
给她挂水
滴速不高于140，她会没事的
Titrate to systolic less than 140. She'll be fine.
卡麦伦，到我办公室来
House: Cameron, meet me in my office.
探通术既冒险又多余...
House: At the risk of sounding redundant...
而且，没错...
and right...again...
她有库欣症
she has Cushing's.
库欣症
Cushing's.
对，也就是说 你扰乱了她的lp
Right...the fact that you mangled her LP has nothing to do with it?
是没有关联的?
Actually, it has everything to do with it.
实际上是完全有关联的
库欣症加上压力等于高血压临界点
Cushing's plus stress equals hypertensive crisis.
干的不错，送了个新手来
Smart move, sending the rookie.
她最初的症状可能由酗酒导致
Her initial symptoms could have been caused by alcohol-induced DIC.
她到达高血压临界点
She hada hypertensive crisis because it's been at least six hours since she hadher last drink.
是因为她已经6个小时没喝酒了
她在戒酒
She's detoxing.
就在我要给她做LP检查的时候么?
The exact same moment that I'm futilely trying to give her an LP?
没错，一个在垂体上肉眼 看不到的瘤倒更象真的
Right, an invisible tumor on her pituitary is much more likely.
如果瘤确实存在其他地方呢?
Chase: What if the tumor is somewhere else?
可能是在肺部或胰脏上长的 促肾上腺皮脂激素瘤
There could be an ACTH-secreting tumor on her lung or pancreas.
太罕见了
It's awfully rare.
那也比肉眼看不见多见
Not as rare as an invisible tumor.
他们干嘛不让你代替福满来负责呢?
Why didn't they put you in charge instead of Foreman?
哦，对，你是杀了那个女人的人
Oh, yeah, you're the guy that killed that woman.
在她死于皮质醇前做个平铺扫描吧
Get a pan-man scan before she dies of cortisol OD.
拜托?
[Whimpers] Please?
好，做吧
Fine, do it.
但如果找不到东西
But when you don't find anything,
就给她吃利眠宁
put her on a Librium taper for the withdrawal and get her a bed in a rehab clinic.
再找个诊所给她做康复好了
肺部正常
Chase: Lungs look clean.
她的淋巴结没有肿大
Her lymph node's not enlarged.
卡迪让福满负责这个部门
Cuddy tapped Foreman to run the department.
都没人问我
- I didn't even get asked. - Neither did I.
- 也没问我 - 你被停职了
- You were suspended. - I was kidding.
我开玩笑呢
It's the irony of women in charge. They don't like other women in charge.
是对女人当权的讥讽
他们就是不喜欢其他女人管事
怎么？你觉得是其他原因么？
Hmph!
What? You think it's something else?
是你自己搞砸了
You sabotaged yourself.
你跟豪斯约会，又跟我睡觉
You went on a date with House. You slept with me.
让你负责这个部门
Putting you in charge of this department is like a sexual harassment suit waiting to happen.
就象是等待性骚扰案件发生一样
是啊，就象我真能 创造个敌对环境似的
Yeah. They're really worried that I'm gonna create a hostile work environment.
没准就是这个问题
Maybe that's the problem.
做主管就象对豪斯说不一样
Being in charge means having to say "no" to House.
你会那样做么?
Would you hire you for that?
安德森强势出场
[On TV] Anderson coming out strong.
他在想什么?
What is he thinking? He watched what Tom Meents just did.
他看到了汤母的作为
你让做的妇科整体核磁共振检查么?
You ordered MRIs for the entire maternity ward?
我当时状态癫狂
I was in a crazy mood.
还好我有个新老板来收拾烂摊子
Good thing I got a new boss to back me up.
尽管我觉得这中间有有用的东西
Although I think one of those is actually necessary.
在你都取消前还是梳理一下吧
Better comb through before you cancel them all.
豪斯，你到底想让我怎样?
What do you expect me to do, House?
放弃？哭？
Quit? Cry?
其实，我希望你能名副其职
Actually, I expect you to act like what you are.
我的雇员、我的属下
My employee. My subordinate.
我的婊子
My bitch.
对啊，既然你好意询问……
Yeah. Well, since you asked nicely--
上帝，我不能相信 我拉下了整年的离职摘要
God. I can't believe I got more than a year behind
得赶紧赶上来
on my discharge summaries. Gotta get caught up.
哦，不，等等
Oh, no. Wait.
我已经没有授权签这些东西了
I'm not authorized to sign these anymore. Only you are.
但你能
放马过来吧，我不会崩溃的
Keep it coming. I'm not gonna break.
扫描显示她的胰脏有问题
Scan showed a mass on her pancreas.
看上去是恶性的，可能不宜动手术
It looks malignant. Probably inoperable.
我看至多挺两个月
I'd give her two months.
从好的方面看，我是对的
[Sighs]
On the bright side, it still means I was right.
豪斯医生在哪?
Where's Dr. House?
福满医生接手了你的病例
Dr. Foreman's overseeing your case.
他认为我跟你说比较恰当
He thought it'd be best if I spoke with you.
我们在你的胰脏发现了一个肿块
We found a mass in your pancreas.
象癌症
It looks like cancer.
也就是说胰脏的东西导致我抽搐?
So something in my pancreas caused me to have a seizure?
或许
Probably. But the bigger point is...
但更重要的问题是...
[Inhales deeply and exhales] A one year survival rate for pancreatic cancer is less than 20%.
胰脏癌症成活超过 一年的病例不足两成
那治疗方案呢?
So what's the treatment?
我们要对肿块进行活检以验明正身
We need to biopsy the mass to see what we're dealing with. And...
然后...
我们会提供选择
Then we can recommend options from there.
听起来不错
Sounds good.
活检需要得到你的同意
I need your consent to do the biopsy.
谢谢，祝我好运吧
Thanks.
Wish me luck.
祝你好运
Good luck.
奇怪，她好像根本没反应似的
Cameron: It was weird. She barely reacted at all.
我会希望人们拥抱我
I've had people hug me
摇摇我
and people take a swing at me.
这有点象她没听见我说话似的
This was more like she didn't even hear me.
放大三倍
Magnify three times.
豪斯援助
House assisting. That is funny.
真有趣
福满要死了真遗憾
Too bad Foreman's gonna die.
下午好
Good afternoon.
我是豪斯医生，我要看你的……
I'm Dr. House.
I'm going to be looking at your...
太好了
Perfect.
请原谅
Excuse me.
我需要福满医生在1号诊疗室督导
I need Dr. Foreman in Exam Room One for a consult.
什么时候开始的?
So, when did this start?
几周前
A couple weeks ago.
我不想怀孕
I didn't want to get pregnant.
杰不愿带避孕套 我就用了避孕胶
Jake's not into rubbers, so I got on the jelly.
你看我是不是过敏还是什么?
You think I'm allergic or something?
你感染了，需要样品
You have an infection. Gonna need a sample.
我带瓶子来了
I brought the jar.
不，我的意思是你的……
No, I meant a sample of your...
好，我们有个神经学问题……
Okay. We have a neurological problem here.
我的脑子有问题么?
There's something wrong with my brain?
哦，对
Oh, yeah.
你穿上吧，我得到需要的了
You can cover yourself up. I got what I need.
怎么了?
What's up?
闻闻
Smell this.
闻起来象阴道
[Sniffs] Smells like vaginosis.
但其实并不是我叫的
But it's not really my call.
太好了，我会记得在你的名字后面 加个金质的星星
Great. I'll be sure to put a gold star by your name on the board.
安妮卡的胰脏癌症活检
Anica's biopsy for pancreatic cancer
是阴性的
was negative.
好，我给你点抗生素
Okay. I'm gonna give you some antibiotics
你要一阵子别过性生活了
and you probably shouldn't have sex for a while.
多久？
How long?
以进化论的基础来说，我认为永远
On an evolutionary basis, I'd recommend forever.
胰脏肿块是良性的
The mass in the pancreas is benign.
可能只是个疤痕组织
It's probably just scar tissue.
好消息，她没病
Good news. She's not sick all. Other than being an alcoholic.
不过是个酒鬼而已
The labs you sent yesterday put her ACTH at 64 pico-grams per milliliter.
昨天你送检的东西
使她分泌64毫克促肾上腺皮质激素
她发库欣症，有事引发了症状
She's got Cushing's. Something set it off.
该是大脑
It's gotta be in her brain.
给她做个静脉取样
Set her up for a venous sampling.
还有另一个可能性
There is another possibility.
小蔡，等等
Chase, hold on.
你怎么能把他训练的这么快的?
How'd you get him trained so fast?
电领子？口袋里有零食么？
Electronic collar?
胰脏活检的报告她都没读
Got treats in your pocket?
She didn't even read the consent form for the pancreatic biopsy.
谁读啊?
Who reads those things?
她不读，也许是因为她知道
Maybe she didn't read it because she KNEW that there was nothing wrong with her.
自己根本就没病
库欣症还有其他解释
There is another explanation for the Cushing's. Maybe she injected herself with the ACTH.
或许是她自己注射的激素
她的举止很象妄想症
Her behavior suggests Munchausen's.
过去的4个月里她有4次入院记录
She's had four hospitalizations in the last four months.
哦，很多入院治疗的记录对你来说 就是没事找事
Well, being hospitalized a lot certainly points to nothing being wrong with you.
她自打入院后就没有任何症状
She's had zero symptoms since she got here.
她的胰脏伤痕累累
The scarring on her pancreas could be be caused from injecting herself with the benzene and setting offthe seizures.
说明她注射苯而导致抽搐
她做过脑外科手术
House: She's had brain surgery.
你可以装胃疼 但无法装出脑部肿瘤
You can fake a stomach ache. You can't fake a brain tumor.
但可以装出个肉眼看不见的来
You can fake an invisible one.
我们该查她的住所找药品和耳咽管
We should check her apartment. Look for medications, syringes.
- 静脉取样更容易 - 也更危险
- Venous sampling's easier. - And more dangerous.
比非法闯入好点吧
Not if you get caught breaking in.
那就别被抓，豪斯
So don't get caught, House.
你觉得卡迪为什么挑福满不挑我?
Why do you think Cuddy picked Foreman over me?
是不是我做错了什么 或需要改进什么
If I done something wrong or if there's something I needed to improve on...
如果我告诉你她想要黑人
Would it make you shut up if I told you she wanted someone black?
是不是可以让你住嘴?
你怎么评价我的领导才能?
How would you describe my leadership skills?
不存在，或很好
Nonexistent. Otherwise excellent.
当领导总比当傻子强吧
There's more to being a leader than being a jerk.
无人知晓
The world will never know.
[Starts engine]
不，没门，刚下完雪
No. No way.
昨天，路挺好
- It just snowed. - Yesterday.
The streets are clear.
我的车在那
My car is right there.
榆树街有路障
There's construction on Elm. Bike'll be faster.
摩托车快些
[Guns the motor]
浴室里都有书
Cameron: There's even books in the bathroom.
要么她就很聪明
Well, either she's very smart or she has a severe fiber deficiency.
要么就是纤维缺乏
"Tuesday 1 pm Opthalmologist,  Dr. Peterson" "Thursday 10 am Gynecologist, Dr. Lachowicz"
她跟她的眼科医生在周二有约
She's got an appointment with her ophthalmologist on Tuesday
周4和妇科医生有约
and an appointment with her gynecologist on Thursday.
同时跟多个医生有约
Multiple appointments with multiple doctors.
妄想症症状
Symptom of Munchausen's.
或者跳出束缚思考
Or, just thinking outside the box here, she has a vagina and trouble reading.
她有个阴道同时阅读有困难
这有3副阅读眼睛 是不同配方的
There's three pairs of reading glasses. Each with different prescriptions.
正可以解释脑瘤压迫视觉神经
Which would be explained by a tumor pressing on the optic nerve.
因为你在为她得癌找佐证
Because you're looking for her to have a tumor.
而你在找...
And you are looking for...
妄想症的佐证
A person with Munchausen's Syndrome
喝电池酸并不需要 他们去眼科医生那里去扩瞳
drinks battery acid. They don't go to an ophthalmologist to get their pupils dilated.
眼科医生也是医生
An ophthalmologist is a doctor. Attention is attention.
注意力是注意力
你联系了几家医院?
How many hospitals have you contacted?
有任何一位医生说她疯了么？ 她不是妄想症
Has one doctor said she's crazy? It's not Munchausen's.
不是你的期待
It's not your call.
如果你觉得她有妄想症
If you think she's got Munchausen's, then obviously you got something to show the man.
那你该有明显的事实给他
一个灌洗器，一瓶激素
A syringe in her apartment. A bottle of ACTH.
妄想症的病人很善于隐藏他们的行踪
Munchausen patients are good at covering their tracks.
哦，对啊，所以我们什么都没找到
Oh, right. So the fact that we found nothing
倒能证明问题了
proves there's something.
看看芝加哥她的医生们的报告啊
Look at the pathology reports from the surgery she had in Chicago.
他们切除了她30％的垂体
They removed 30% of her pituitary.
他们没发现瘤
They found no tumor.
可能是医生没找到
It's possible the surgeons just missed it.
我的意思是那种手术 切开然后希望
I mean that kind of surgery. You're just cutting and hoping.
当然，我们都对
Of course! We're both right. Excellent solution. Everybody's happy.
完美的结论，大家都高兴
拜托，提高点，福满
Come on. Step up, Foreman.
如果你觉得我对 让我往病人脑袋里插针
If you think I'm right, order me to stick a needle in her brain.
如果你觉得卡麦伦对 送病人回家
If you think Cameron's right, send the patient home.
她要么死，要么活
Either she'll be fine, or she'll die.
征求她的意见，做静脉取样
Do the venous sampling. Get her consent.
干的不错，老板 可以保住你的屁股了
Nice move, boss. Way to cover your ass.
我只是赞同你罢了
I just agreed with you.
并不是你觉得我对
Not because you think I'm right.
你只是选择了安全通道
You're just taking the safe route.
你是软脚虾
You're a wuss.
别担心，我会守口如瓶的
Don't worry. Your secret's safe with me.
嘿，威尔森 猜刚才福满干了什么?
House: Hey, Wilson! Guess what Foreman just did?
嗨
Hi.
这是往你脑子里放置导管的同意书
This is a consent form to stick a wire into your brain.
对医院来说这是很重要的程序
It's important for hospitals to get these signed for procedures that are completely unnecessary.
但其实根本没必要
那你干嘛还做?
Then why are you doing it?
因为你精神有问题
Because you're mentally ill.
你为吸引医生注意给自己
You injected yourself with ACTH to induce Cushing's to get attention doctors.
注射激素导致抽搐
到目前为止有效
And so far it's worked.
我要见其他医生
I'd like to see another doctor.
我没给你要的东西么?
I'm not giving you what you want?
我不要个婊子
I don't want a bitch.
签了这个表格，我就走
Just sign the forms, okay, and I'll get out of here.
希望无论你给自己注射什么
Hopefully for you, what ever you injected yourself with won't wear off
在一个真正关心你的医生
before you get fun of a caring and concerned doctor cutting into your head.
打开你的脑袋前别用光了
你选我让豪斯感觉悲惨是吧？
You chose me to make House miserable, didn't you?
很明显他让你觉得很悲惨
Apparently he's making YOU miserable.
真感人
That's impressive.
另请高明吧
Find someone else.
不，6年了，我头一次可以拿到
No.
For the first time in six years I'm getting copied on all experimental tests and procedures.
试验单副本和所有程序副本
问诊时间充足
Clinic hours have been logged and completed.
在豪斯听政前你给了我4个月
You've given me four months of House's dictations
使我可以找保险公司算账
so I can finally bill insurance companies.
而我只证明了豪斯可以让我很悲惨
I only did that stuff to prove he couldn't make me miserable.
干的不错
Well, way to go.
现在所有人都得其所哉了 连豪斯也是
Now everybody's getting what they need. Even House.
他可以扮演科学狂人 这个部门运转顺畅
He gets to play mad scientist, and this department runs smoothly.
而我在接下来的3个星期 还得继续卡在那么
So I'm stuck with this for the next three weeks.
没准更长呢
Maybe longer.
如果这一切不是假装你会有兴趣么?
Would you be interested if this wasn't just pretend?
妈妈怎么说?
What did Mommy say?
我袜子里没有糖果
I don't get any candy in my stocking.
病人准备做静脉取样么?
Patient being prepped for the venous sampling?
对
Yeah.
精神有问题的病人正准备 进行一个无意义的程序
Mentally ill patient is right on track for a pointless procedure.
好，我们知道你的异议了
Yeah, we get your objection. [Phone starts ringing]
福满
Foreman.
你肯定吗?
Are you sure?
那没理由，再查一下
That doesn't make any sense. Check it again.
我们得暂停取样检查了
Haw! We gotta delay the venous sampling.
为什么？ 她的尿变橙色了么？
Why? Her urine turning orange?
你怎会知道?
How would you know that?
因为那是利福平的功效
Because that's what rifampin does.
她并没用抗生素?
She's not on antibiotics?
但如果一个妄想症病人 发觉她的把戏要被揭穿了
But if a Munchausen's patient thinks she's about get busted,
她看到一个标着“危险”字样 的药瓶就会拿几片
she sees pills labeled "Dangerous: might cause seizures," she might grab a couple.
而如果那个贴标签的 瓶子碰巧是抗生素
And if that label were accidentally on a bottle of antibiotics
而那个瓶子又碰巧是放在了她屋里...
and if that bottle were accidentally left in her room...
- 你陷害她? - 没准
- You set her up? - Might have.
是妄想症
It's Munchausen's.
这些都是她自找
All this she did to herself.
我不知道你到底说什么
I don't  what the hell you're talking about.
我抽筋了
I had a seizure. I'm sick. I need your help.
我病了，我需要你的帮助
不是这个科
Not from this department.
利福平半衰期3个小时
The half-life of rifampin is three hours. After that, you'll get your psych referral
然后会推荐你精神科医生
和你的账单
and your discharge papers.
你知道，不因为你把手指插到喉咙里
You know, just because you stick your fingers down your throat
我们大家都被你搞了
doesn't mean the rest of us are screwed up.
我看当合作失败后 你就会变得敌意了
I guess when cooperation fails, you move onto hostility.
我不是蓄意这样做的
I didn't do this to myself.
100% 承诺
Chase: 100% commitment.
由说谎的人签署
Sign of a good liar.
也是反社会的人签署的
[Scoffs] Also the sign of a sociopath.
你在干嘛?
What are you doing?
改正你最后一个笔记
Correcting your last note.
我们不能放走她，她有病
We can't discharge her, she's sick.
有人告诉你你笔迹象姑娘么？
Anybody ever tell you you write like a girl?
什么?
What?
你对橙色尿液有其他解释么?
You got some other explanation for orange urine?
- 是妄想症 - 对，但不完全
- It's Munchausen's. - Correct, but not complete.
你就是无法承认她使你惨败的事实
You just don't wanna admit that she skunked you.
叫“狼来了”的孩子
At the end of "The Boy Who Cried Wolf"
结果是狼真的来了
the wolf really does come.
他吃了孩子、羊还有孩子的父母
And he eats the sheep and the boy and his parents.
羊没吃父母
- The wolf doesn't eat the parents. - It does when I tell it.
- 我讲的时候就吃了 - 现在不由你讲故事，我在讲
You're not telling the story now. I am.
看，我查了她的记录
Look, I checked her records.
她所有的住院记录所为理由不同
All her hospitalizations were for different things.
脑瘤、昏厥、皮疹、抽搐
Brain tumor, fainting spells, skin rashes, seizures.
她的验血记录到处都是
She's had every blood test known to man and the results were all over the map.
结果只有一个：低ACT
There's only one constant. Low HCT.
贫血是真的
The anemia's real.
能导致那个症状的药品 她能吃到的多了
There's a million things she could have taken to have done that.
对，也可能根本就是月经闹的
True. Could just be her M.O.
她自找了两种病，一种老变 另一种从来不变
She self-induces two illnesses. One always changes, one never does.
又或许她得了妄想症和 再生障碍型贫血
Or maybe, she has Munchausen's and aplastic anemia.
也就是说，没有适当的治疗
Which would mean without the proper treatment, she'll continue to get sicker, weaker,
她会变得越来越虚弱、严重 之至内出血而死
eventually she'll start bleeding internally and die.
- 她不会变得更重 - 她会的
- She's not getting sicker. - She will.
如果她的骨髓在衰亡 那整个血液系统都会出问题的
If her bone marrow was dying, the entire blood panel would be affected.
- 她的白血球读数正常 - 目前而言
- Her white count's normal. - So far.
我们要做骨髓活检
We need to do a bone marrow biopsy.
- 不，不做检查了 - 你看
- No. No more tests. - Look.
你看，如果你用妄想症把她 踢到一边
You kick her to the curb with a Munchausen's diagnosis,
今后保证再也没有 医生会相信她的话了
you're guaranteeing that no doctor will ever listen to her again.
我们做再多的检查也只是喂养了 她的精神而已
We do more tests, we'll only be feeding her psychosis.
我们给予她越多注意，她就越贪婪
The more attention we give her, the more she'll want.
如果她不知道我们在检查她如何?
What if she doesn't know we're testing her?
豪斯，你错了 认命吧
House. You were wrong. Live with it.
早前的检查还剩下些血液
There's probably some blood left over from previous tests.
只验血无法证实再生障碍性贫血
Blood tests alone can't confirm aplastic anemia.
对，我知道，所以才要做骨髓活检
Yes, I know. That's why I wanna do a bone marrow biopsy.
血液检查可以显示系统疾病 或滤过病毒或毒素的成因
The blood tests could show a systemic disease, or a virus or toxin that could be the cause.
好，你想要多查点血么？ 把你自己敲晕吧
Fine. You wanna test the extra blood? Knock yourself out.
但病人已经超限了
But the patient is off-limits.
如果结果是阳性的……
And if the results are positive...
我可以活检么?
I get my biopsy?
是条安全的路
It's a safe way to go.
我需要做所有检查和PCR
I need all of these tests and a PCR done on this sample.
只能用这些样品
需要更多血
You're gonna need more blood.
病人没血了
Patient's empty.
那我就不能做
Then I can't do it.
- 你可以试试 - 我还想试试做名模呢
You can try.
You can try to look like Salma Hayek.
可那是不会发生的
It's not gonna make it happen.
你或许没有名模的屁股
You may not have Salma's ass, but she doesn't have your eyes.
可她没有你的眼睛啊
对，是啊
Yeah, right.
你多久要?
How soon do you need it?
韦森大夫，我能私下跟你谈谈么?
[Knocking on door]
Dr. Wilson. Can I talk to you about something in confidence?
当然
Of course.
- 关于豪斯 - 哦，那算了
- It's about House. - Oh. Then no.
好吧
Fine.
我什么都不说
I won't say anything.
你认为豪斯有可能把我
Do you think there's any way
当成他的真老板么?
House would take me seriously as his boss?
哦，这是从何而来啊?
Uh...where is this coming from?
卡迪没说什么么?
Did Cuddy say something?
我们谈了，她提的
We talked. She intimated.
而你征求我的意见去篡他的权?
And you want my advice on how to usurp him?
在远古你需要袍儿、
It's very ancient Rome. He'll need a toga, of course. A...
剑……
sword.
不是政变，是找到与他共存的方法
It's not a coup.
I just wanna figure out some way we can work together.
我的意思是从管理角度我运作团队
I mean, I keep the team running from an administrative point of view.
豪斯无需应付红胶带
House doesn't have to deal with the red tape.
- 双赢 - 我肯定他也那么看
- It's a win-win. - I'm sure he'll see it that way.
你对于接近他,
You have any advice on how to approach him,
应付他有任何建议么?
- how to deal with the guy? - No.
没有
但你不会告诉他我们谈过是吧?
But you won't tell him we talked?
不会
No.
根本没门这会发生的
There is no way this is gonna happen.
哦，他多么甜蜜
[Singing The Beatles' "Aint She Sweet"] # Oh, ain't he sweet #
看他走在大街上
# See him walkin' down that street #
所以我充满信心的问
# So I ask you very confidentially #
# Ain't he sweet #
艾泼指数到顶了
Epstein-Barr titers are through the roof.
最普通的病毒导致了再障贫血
Most common viral cause of aplastic anemia.
我说的是...
So what I'm saying is...
只向目标望一眼
# Just cast an eye in his direction #
哦，我，我的天，多专业
# Oh me, oh my, ain't that perfection #
胎儿血红蛋白也提高了
Fetal hemoglobin's also elevated.
对，一点点，可能……
Yeah, just a wee bit.
哦，可以在镰状细胞中看出来
- Could indicate... - Uh, you see that in Sickle Cell.
不是所有的镰状细胞病人是黑人
Not all Sickle Cell patients are black.
她其他的血样并未显示镰状细胞
None of her other blood panels showed any sign of Sickle Cell.
也就是说昨天发生了什么突变
Which means either something's changed drastically since yesterday,
或者这不是她的血液
- or this isn't her blood. - Oh course it is!
当然是
比喻性的
Metaphorically.
看，我不能再做检查了
Look, I couldn't do the tests.
我试了，但血液不够
I tried, and there wasn't enough blood left over.
你就让我做活检吧
You just let me do the biopsy.
没门，我刚复职
Chase: No way.
I just got back from a suspension.
如果不是我，你就被炒了
And if it wasn't for me, you would have been fired.
你干嘛不自己去搞样品?
Why don't you just get the sample yourself?
从几时起你开始在乎老板说的话了?
Since when have you cared what your boss said?
我不在乎他们说什么 我在乎他们做什么
I don't care what anybody says, I care what they do.
现在，需要黑白分明
And right now, Blackpoleon Blackaparte has got the nurses on red alert.
他们给护士发了红色警报 不允许我接近病人
I can't get into the patient's room.
所以，来吧，我吸引敌人的火力
So come on. I'll draw the enemy fire,
你走侧翼，进去搞到骨髓样品
you outflank them, get in there, get the bone marrow sample.
不能
Can't.
你更怕谁?
Who are you more afraid of?
我不怕福满，我跟他意见相同
I'm not afraid of Foreman. I agree with him. All the tests back him up.
所有检查都支持他
All the tests have not been done.
并没完成所有检查
你该知道那黑家伙的统治是暂时的吧
You do realize that Blackaparte's reign is only temporary.
我也知道无论我怎么做
I also realize that no matter what I do, you're still gonna treat me like crap.
你都还是会象对待废物一样的对待我
废物是相对的
Crap is a relative term.
我甚至没能进她的房间
I never even made it into the room.
才要了一个套针管护士就叫了主治医
Nurses called the attending as soon as a Trocar was ordered.
你用了她的真名?
You used her real name?
我刚签了你病人的账单
I just processed your patient's discharge papers.
她正要出院
She's on her way out right now.
哎
Whoa! Whoa. Whoa.
等等
Wait up.
没事了，她要留下
It's all right. She's gonna stay.
- 太好了 - 哦，咬我吧
- Wonderful. - Oh, bite me!
我 不想再听混话了
I don't need to hear the riot act again.
那再做一个试验呢?
How would you like another medical test?
- 什么? - 坐
- What? - Sit.
为什么?
Why?
那样你晕过去的时候不会 磕碎你的头骨
So you don't crack your skull when you pass out.
你就听话吧
Just do it.
- 你知道秋水仙碱是什么么? - 不
- You know what colchicine is? - No.
别在意，是加味的
Well, don't feel bad. It's for gout.
跟你的假装症状毫无关系
It's got nothing to do with anything you've ever pretended to have.
- 我没假装 - 闭嘴
- I'm not pretending... - Shut up.
秋水仙碱大量杀死你的白血球 不留痕迹
Colchicine decimates your white blood cells
and leaves almost no trace.
用此假装入院很高明
It's great for faking your way into hospitals.
- 我没假装…… - 闭嘴
- I didn't fake my way... - Shut up.
你经年累月这样做
You've beeing this for years.
别担心，这也许不是你的错
Don't worry, it's probably not your fault.
在你小的时候，你有个近亲有慢性病
When you were a kid, you had a close relative who had a chronic disease,
可能是姐妹
probably your sister.
当你被忽视的时候 你看到她得到的注意
You saw all the attention she got while you were left alone, ignored.
而那当真把你伤害了
And it really seriously crewed you up.
- 我没有…… - 闭嘴
- I do not have a relative... - Shut up!
我给你你想要的
I'm trying to give you what you want.
挽救你的生命
And save your life.
你得了再障贫血
You have aplastic anemia.
什么，你想吓唬我么?
What, are you trying to scare me now?
也就是说你不光只脑子有毛病
It means you're not just sick in the head.
问题是你的其他部分良好
The problem is, the rest of you appears well.
所以我需要让你看上去病的很重
So I've got to make you seem as sick as you're supposed to be
我得给你注射与你症状相符的药物 使你看上去病情严重
by injecting you with a drug
that simulates symptoms that you actually have.
你需要知道的是……
All you need to know is...
你击中了妄想症的筹码
you've hit the Munchausen's jackpot.
我会给你一份胰岛素鸡尾酒让你抽搐
I'm gonna give you a cocktail of insulin for a seizure
用秋水仙碱来杀死白血球
and colchicine to kill your white count,
这就会完全证实 我关于再障贫血的诊断
this will absolutely confirm my diagnosis of aplastic anemia.
有一个小问题
There is one...small catch.
如果你真做了什么导致自己贫血
If you've actually done something to yourself to cause the anemia,
那我就错了
then I'm wrong.
而如果我做了我要做的
And if I do what I plan to do,
那治疗会导致你死亡而不是生存
then the treatment will kill you instead of saving you.
所以我需要知道
So I need to know.
除了胰岛素和激素
Have you been taking anything besides the insulin, the ACTH,
以及卡麦伦留下的药以外还吃了什么?
and the pills Cameron left in your room?
没
No.
好，把胳膊给我
Good.
Give me your arm.
是我妈妈
It was my mom.
她得了ms
She had MS.
她总出入医院
She was in and out of hospitals all the time.
人们总在为她做事
People were always trying to do things for her.
给她拿吃的，帮她梳头...
Bring her food or brush her hair, or...
让她快乐
make her happy.
人们记挂她
People cared.
我16岁时她死了
She died when I was 16.
然后就谁都没了
Then there was no one.
哦吼
Boo hoo.
你去哪?
Where are you going?
哦，当事情发生时我不能在场
Well, I obviously can't be around when it happens.
你要干嘛？你就打算……
Well, what are you gonna do? You're just gonna...
放松，你知道细节
Relax. You know the drill.
总有人路过，你会没事的
People walk by here all the time. You'll be fine.
她又抽筋了
**So fairly off the door and she has another seizure.
她肯定是在出去的时候 顺手拿了点胰岛素
She must've somehow grabbed insulin on her way out.
等她稳定了，我们得把她弄走
Once she's stable, we need to get her out of here before she does more damage to herself.
在她再伤害自己之前.
我们不能
We can't.
她白血球下降了
Her white count's down.
对不起，我错过了
Sorry, I missed that.
理奇马丁音乐会后听力下降了
Hearing's been off since the Ricky Martin concert.
有人踢了我的头
Some cholo kicked me in the head.
白血球、血总值和血小板都没了
White count, hematocrit, and platelets are all off.
她的骨髓关闭了
Her bone marrow's shutting down. She actually has aplastic anemia.
她真有再障贫血
说什么?
Say what?
-她其他数据都没事 - 数据狗屁
Cameron: All her other labs show nothing that would...
好的诊断专家可以从数据中找问题
Lab ***. A good diagnostician reads between the labs.
你对了
You were right.
嘿，我们可不是在这抱怨
Hey, hey, hey. We're not here to play the blame game.
会发生这样的事
These things happen.
有时医生会把病人撵出去受死
Sometimes doctors send people out on the street to die
在被别的医生警告后依然把病人 撵出去受死
after other doctors warn them that they're sending people out on the street to die.
你不可能知道
There's no way you could know.
我去给她这个消息
I'll go give her the news.
你是谁?
Who are you?
我是福满医生
I'm Dr. Foreman. I'm in charge of your case.
我负责你的病例
你得了再障贫血
You have aplastic anemia.
意味着你的骨髓失效了
Which means your bone marrow has shut down.
你的身体拒绝造血
And your body can't make new blood anymore.
你肯定吗？
Are you sure?
我查了你的旧病例
I went back and checked your old records.
是合理的
It makes sense.
再障贫血已经发展几个月了
The aplastic anemia's apparently been developing for months.
我很抱歉，我们该早发现的
I'm sorry, we should've caught it earlier.
那……
So...
并不是最近的白血球读数导致的……
It's not just the latest white count that's leading you to feel this...
我知道这很可怕
I know this is scary.
但骨髓移植可以治愈
But a bone marrow transplant could cure you.
骨髓移植会要我命
A marrow transplant could kill me.
还有个方法是周换血
The other option is weekly blood transfusions.
注射gcsf
Injections of GCSF.
是终生制的
- It's a life-long regimen. - Yeah, I don't want that.
对，我不要
你肯定?
Are you sure?
我不想狠心
I-I don't want to be ruel here, but...
但你做了很多努力得到这样的注意
you jumped through a lot of hoops to get this sort of attention.
我就是想健康
I just wanna be healthy.
而你病的时候就没那么多乐趣了
It's not so much fun when you're actually sick.
不
No.
我们会……查查登记处
We'll um... we'll check the registry.
看是否有捐赠者
See if there's a donor match.
谢谢
Thank you.
在找到新骨髓前 我们要杀死所有老的
We have to kill all the old bone marrow before we give you the new stuff.
你就没有免疫系统了
You'll have no immune system.
我们会把你留在无菌室 确保一切都死了
We'll keep you in a sterile room for two weeks to make sure everything's dead.
然后给你捐赠的骨髓
Then we'll give you the donor marrow.
然后再用数周使其稳定
It'll take another couple of weeks until it takes hold.
你感觉不到什么
You won't feel a thing.
如果你觉得不舒服，或需要什么
If you get uncomfortable for any reason I need to talk, don't yell.
别喊
Walls are four inches thick. Lead.
墙有4英尺厚
向前
Use the microphone.
用麦克风
准备好了么?
Are you ready?
好
Okay.
[Irradiation starts]
豪斯医生在哪?
Where's Dr. House?
关掉
Turn it off.
- 怎么了? - 她在里面多久了?
[Monitor starts beeping] Now what?
3分钟，怎么了?
How long has she been in there?
Three minutes. What's going on?
她没有再障贫血
She doesn't have aplastic anemia.
她感染了
She has an infection.
不，她的白血球高的惊人
No. Her white count would be through the roof. Hers is one the floor.
这就是
身体干疯狂的事
- Well, the body does crazy things. - "The body does crazy things."
"身体干疯狂的事"
那就都解释了
Well, that explains everything.
她不发热
She had no fever.
因为她自己制造库欣症压制免疫系统
'Cause her self-inflicted Cushing's suppressed her immune system.
使她不发热，抑制感染
Stopped her from having a fever. Hid the infection.
梭菌可导致瘀伤、细胞分裂和贫血
Clostridium perfringens could cause the bruises, schistocytes, the anemia...
都能解释除了白血球的问题
Explains everything except the white count.
查证比摧毁她的免疫系统安全的多
Augmentin is a lot safer than destroying her immune system. Why don't we try that?
干嘛不试试?
你要选择安全路径?
Ww-you're taking the safe course?
怎么回事?
What's going on?
白血球低有很多原因
There's lots of explanations for a low white count.
说一种符合她的症状
Name one that fits her case.
秋水仙碱
Colchicine.
我猜她能拿到
I figure that she'd gotten her hands on it and, uh, just self-medicated.
就自己给药了
她多聪明
That's brilliant of her!
用了正好可以证实你诊断的药
Take the exact medication that would confirm your diagnosis.
人们会做疯狂的事
People do crazy things.
你给她用药 违背她的意愿以证实自己对?
You injected her against her will just so you could be right?
- 她同意 - 她精神有病
- She consented. - She's mentally ill!
她闻上去非常甜美
But she smells oh so sweet.
我让说她严重的时候她该变严重
She would've gotten sicker when I said she was gonna get sicker,
而卡麦伦给了她抗生素
except Cameron dosed her with antibiotics. Just hold this.
拿好
- Is everything okay? - Pull my finger.
一切都好么?
拉我的手指
[Gasps]
[Sniffs]
象葡萄似的
Grapey.
你有细菌
You have a bacterium.
大家都有
It's on all of us. But...
而你给自己库欣症的伤痕 却给了它一个家
the bruises you gave yourself with the Cushing's made a lovely home.
细菌搬进来，做了邻居
Bacteria moved in,
parked their cars on the lawn. There goes the neighborhood.
邻居的意思是跟你的内脏
By "neighborhood" I mean your internal organs.
那么我们是不是该给她做点什么?
So, should we put her on the Augmentin, boss?
还是你觉得她自己注射了葡萄?
Or do you think she injected herself with grapes? [Sniffs]
我喜欢闻这个
I love the smell of pus in the morning.
闻上去象...
Smells like...
胜利的味道
victory.
如果你正式提议
If you were serious about the offer,
我会严肃接受
I'm serious about accepting.
我想掌管部门
I'd like to run the department.
而且你自己说事情很顺畅
And you said it yourself, things run smooth.
除了豪斯在你背后的行为
Except for the part where House went behind your back
给病人用胰岛素和秋水仙碱
and KO'd the patient with insulin and colchicine.
没理由怀疑是感染
There was no reason to suspect an infection.
连豪斯也没那么怀疑
Even House didn't think it was an infection.
你也会做同样的事
You would've done the same thing I did.
而我同样也会错
And I'd be just as wrong.
豪斯的作为很疯狂 却保存了她的性命
What House did was insane. But he saved her life.
他很幸运
He got lucky.
他让她承认自己有病
He got her to admit she's got a problem.
她同意做院外处理
She's agreed to out-patient treatment.
他太走运了
He gets lucky a lot.
你真的有意要给我这个工作么?
Did you ever really intend to give me this job?
还是你只是在阻止我走下坡路？
Or were you just trying to stop me from stepping down?
你还有两周负责
You've got two more weeks in charge.
希望下个病例能成功
Hopefully the next case will go better.
她本来会死
She should've died.
豪斯不是英雄
House is not a hero.
敢于打破陋习的人
A person who has the guts to break a bad rule,
才是英雄
they're a hero.
豪斯没打破陋习，他忽视它们
House doesn't break rules. He ignores them.
他不是罗莎帕可
He's not Rosa Parks.
他是无政府主义者
He's an anarchist.
他所维护的是
All he stands for is the right
所见所得所需
for everyone to grab whatever they want whenever they want.
你告诉医生那没事
You tell doctors that's okay,
你的死亡率会高过屋顶
your mortality rate is gonna go through the roof.
福满负责的事挺好
Kinda digging this whole Foreman-in-charge thing.
你知道
You know.
让我有空看连续剧
It frees me up to watch my soaps.
下午看电影
Catch a movie in the afternoon.
跟你一起吃晚餐
Have lunch with you.
对，对你是个大变化
Yeah, that's a big change for you.
现在卡迪要看的是福满的屁股 不是我的了
Now Cuddy's up Foreman's ass, not mine.
# Carols everywhere...#
你受不了福满做你的老板
You couldn't live with Foreman as your boss.
为什么不?
Why not?
人会变，你知道
People can change, you know.
# Sleigh bells in the air #
# Beauty everywhere... #
你的白血球降下去了
- White count is way down. - Oh.
我们会接纳你
We're going to need to admit you. Just run a few more tests.
再做点检查
Whatever you think is best.
你觉得好就做吧
# Christmas time is here... #
贝尔蒙最后的比赛
Last race at the Belmont. Put it all on the 5. To win.
都押在5号赢
# Oh that we could always see # Transcript : Raceman Synchro : Vaccine
# Such spirit through the year # www.forom.com